Now, it's started!
This is TOKIMEKI BALLON METAL JASHOW
TV!
We are back!
What are we doing today?
What are we doing this week?
This week, we are going to do...
This week, we are going to do the
Akichan King Final!
We had a fair competition last time.
Are you confident?
We are going to do the Akichan King
Final!
We were in a tight spot last time.
I hope we can do well this time.
Kanami, please explain the rules.
We are going to ask Akichan a lot of
questions.
Akichan has already answered the
We are going to think about the answer
and answer it.
And...
We will give you the point for the
correct answer.
Cute!
I'm Tsuda.
Unfortunately, the person who didn't
get the point is going to be punished.
Who is going to be punished?
Last time, we did the Akichan King
Final.
We did the Akichan King Final with a
lot of mistakes.
We are going to think about the point
of the word.
I'm Kanami.
Kanami is going to do her best to make
the word.
It's a little difficult.
I can't say it if it's a tongue
twister.
I'm going to do my best to make the
word.
Let's do it!
Here we go.
The first one.
What is your favorite hairstyle?
Now?
I don't know.
Not the length.
Now?
Hair style.
Simple.
Simple?
I got it.
Is it simple?
Yes.
It's a hairstyle, isn't it?
I often do it.
Maybe it's not Aki-chan and IEVA.
It's not!
Then, it might be wrong.
I don't know.
Simple?
I can't say the answer.
If you say simple...
I think I know.
I think I know, too.
I think so, too.
Time up!
Please read the question in order.
What is the name of the Japanese singer
who sang the song of the same name?
Ponytail.
Ponyodan.
That's all.
I thought it was Ponyodan.
I saw the picture, but I couldn't
remember.
I don't think it's the same.
I used to be Pony.
What's that illustration?
I like Pony.
I like that illustration.
I like Odan...
No, Odan.
I like Odan.
I like Shinbun.
I like Asuka.
I haven't done it recently.
I did it with Less and Pony.
Less and Pony.
I like Pony, too.
It's wrong!
Pony 5 is wrong.
Let's go to the next question.
Please look forward to the next video.
What is your favorite hairstyle?
My favorite hairstyle is...
Drawing with Cameras!
Juri seems confident because she's
drawing most of the thing at the end but
the liberties are not really as
Clarissa's així
It would be nice to use a full-on style
I'm not sure
Speaking of areas Seriousness
Everyone got 10 with the large Giulia
It's a massacre
So the tie-breakers are ZERO.
Please do your best!
Next time
Here is the second question
What is the song that Aki-chan listens
to the most?
The hint is that it's a recent song
What?
Will this song come out?
Recently?
Recently!
If you say recently, it's not that.
I got it.
Then, isn't it only this?
What?
Wide-span recently.
Wide-span...
Then, it's not this.
Isn't it this?
If you say recently, it's only this.
Recently...
That's what you mean, right?
What do you mean?
Do you know?
I think I know.
It's the same.
I think so, too.
I think I know.
What are you listening to?
I'm listening to a different song.
Are you ready?
July, was it?
Keep your time.
I like it!
July cider!
But it's time to sing!
It's time!
I'll do my best!
Please!
What is your favorite song?
My favorite song is...
I recently listen to Sukio!
How long have you been listening to it?
I've been listening to it a lot
recently.
I like it!
Yay!
I like Sukio!
Mochimochi ~!
Let's move on to the third question.
What did Aki-chan eat for dinner?
This is hard!
I have a hint.
A hint?
My daily life.
I think I know.
What about Aki-chan?
Did you say that on Aki-chan's YouTube
channel?
No, I didn't.
Then, you should say that.
Daily life?
What is it?
Always...
It's not always like this.
What is it?
Let's do this.
Maybe it's a school day.
I'm like that.
I don't know.
What is that?
Do you eat it at school?
I don't know.
It's not interesting.
It's not interesting at all.
I've got two questions.
I'm not confident.
What?
Shall we start?
Let's start.
What do you eat at school?
I don't eat it.
I don't eat it, either.
Bread.
Meat.
I like all of them.
I like meat.
You're saying all of them are
different.
Let's start.
Please watch this video and follow us
on Twitter!
What did you eat for breakfast?
I didn't eat anything!
Awesome
That's amazing. Good thing Giri zo
Sugar wouldn't come.
This was so weird.
Yeah, I found it terrible.
You Iont know what gigs would Iike.
I eat all the time.
Come on, you used to gibiibo?
Dice would be great.
I used to sit in front of the mirror on
stage.
Yes, like a superhero.
It's my first time to come here.
It's been a while.
Next, let's go to the fourth question.
This is bad, I can't get it at all.
This is the fourth question.
What is Aki's favorite Pokemon?
I don't know.
This is difficult.
Isn't that a Pokemon?
I don't know.
I don't know the name of the Pokemon.
Can I say the first character?
I know what you like.
Do you?
I like Pokemon.
Wait, wait, wait.
But you said it in the video of the
infinite dynamo.
Wait, do you really know?
I've been playing Pokemon lately.
I'm playing with electric current.
What are you talking about?
Wait, wait.
I'm talking about my extra story.
Please subscribe to this channel.
What is the name of the character in
the anime?
It's a mystery.
Pochama.
Pochama?
Who is Pochama?
It's funny.
I feel like I became a hero.
Let's answer.
Please subscribe to this channel.
What is your favorite Pokemon?
My favorite Pokemon is Mew!
I like Mew!
It's a new one.
I've never heard of it.
I've seen it in a movie.
It's a movie.
Mew!
I want to talk, but this is coming
slowly.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Next, the fifth question.
This is difficult.
Aki-chan, this is difficult.
I have information I don't know.
Next, this is easy.
What is the height of Aki-chan's body
measured by the star graph?
This is easy.
What is the length of the wall?
I don't know.
How long is the wall?
About the same length as the mirror.
I can answer that.
How long is the wall?
It is about the ceiling.
Is it the ceiling?
Is the wall long?
How long is the wall?
It is about the same length as the
wall.
Is it the same length?
I think so.
It may be different.
I am not confident.
It is not small.
Is it the same length?
I don't think so.
The answer is...
What is it?
Please show us the answer.
153.5 cm.
That's small.
I'm 151 cm.
154.5 cm.
153.5 cm.
She's bigger than me.
I'm 154.1 cm.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm sorry.
I'm here!
Did you get the answer?
Please look at the QR code.
How tall is Aki's height in the
official profile of Stardust?
153.5 cm!
I'm pretty tall, so I'm sure everyone
is right.
See you next time!
You're so excited!
I didn't think you'd be so excited.
But I guess you got used to it.
That's all.
Ruru!
Oh no.
The sixth question.
What is Aki's favorite color?
Oh no.
I believe you.
Wait, which one is it?
I have a feeling.
I can only think of one.
What?
Wait, which one?
I think I know.
What?
But I can write it down.
I can't decide.
I can't.
I'm going to be a punishment.
One.
Ageless.
Yes, yes.
Oh, that's what you mean.
Bearable
Haru is betting on Shizuya.
Wait, what should I do?
I don't want to do this.
Haru, you haven't won anything yet.
I haven't won anything yet.
My juniors are playing games with me.
White.
Black.
Light blue.
I won!
I lost.
I was confused between white and black.
I was confused between light blue and
white.
black.
I was confused between light blue and
white.
You look hungry.
You look cute.
What's your favorite color?
My favorite color is white.
White!
I was confused between light blue and
white.
You're right!
You're amazing!
You were right when you sang the first
part.
I was confused between light blue and
white.
I like black, too.
I like white, too.
You're kind.
The current score is...
Nanamin 2, Churiya 3, Hita 1, Hayu 0,
Yuri 1.
It's tough.
I'm glad you got the right answer.
Let's do our best from now on.
Let's do our best!
I want to get at least one point.
The next question is...
What is Aki's fastest time in the 50m
race?
I've heard of it.
I've never heard of it.
What is Kiri?
I don't know.
How many seconds did she run?
I don't remember.
What grade were you in?
It depends.
What grade?
How many seconds did she run?
12 seconds.
12 seconds?
Yes.
I don't have a fast image.
I think I'm the fastest.
I think so.
I don't think so.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Wait, I'm not wearing a hat.
I'm wearing a normal hair.
8.3.
I'm sorry.
I can't tell if I wear this.
I can't tell.
Please open the bag.
9.
What is the fastest time of 50m run of
Maki?
The fastest.
But I'm slow, so 8.4 seconds.
So close!
No, I'm 8.6 seconds.
That's fast.
The fastest.
So I thought I was a little faster.
That's how fast I was.
That's good.
So close!
I'm going to be a little slower.
Can I have two?
So close!
I'm sorry.
It's difficult, so I can't help it.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Let's move on to the next one.
How wide is your favorite mask?
How wide is it?
It's normal.
I think I know.
I don't know how wide it is.
Use your hand.
Stand up.
I don't know.
I'm using it now.
I didn't know the width of the mask was
this small.
I don't know how many centimeters the
width of the mask is.
It's better to have up to 1.5 cm.
It's big.
I don't know.
Wait.
How much is it?
Please subscribe to this channel.
I don't know.
I wonder if it's this big.
It's difficult.
I don't know the width of the mask.
Is it this big?
It's not.
I don't know.
The word mask is a very big weapon.
The score is up.
The score is 32.
What?
What is this?
I know what it is.
This is bad.
Why?
It's a mental attack.
I'm sorry.
It's strong.
It's a mental attack.
I'm sorry.
Next, Ayaka.
The score is 12.5.
The score is 10.5.
The score is 16.5.
The score is 14.5.
What?
Kanami is the best.
The score is 11.5.
The score is 12.5.
I might be right.
What is the width of your favorite
mask?
Can you guess?
It's 14.5cm.
I'm so good at it.
I've been looking up the width of my
favorite mask.
I think my favorite mask is big.
So, I looked up the width of my
favorite mask and compared it with the
width of my favorite mask.
I think this width is good.
You have other favorite masks, don't
you?
By the way, the width of my favorite
mask is 9.5cm.
I'm so good at it.
You are the best.
I've been looking up the width of my
favorite mask.
What is the width of your favorite
mask?
It's 32cm.
You are not big.
You are so good at it.
How many people are there in Kanamin?
I don't know.
Kanamin has 2 points, Chie has 3
points, Seika has 1 point, Ohayou has 0
points, and Hiyori has 2 points.
Kanapio has 1 point.
Let's do our best.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Next question!
Aki-chan likes kinako recently. How do
you eat it?
Kinako?
Do you eat it?
Who eats it?
Please subscribe to my channel!
32.
How to eat?
There are many ways to eat.
This one?
This one.
Then, this one.
It's interesting.
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to our channel!
Please keep an eye on her.
Recommend videos of Mocham That Mocham
is in,
Tamakku Sacho
Alright then, we will reveal the
results.
Ignorant mom
OK!
We'll present you...
Real treat
Hello there.
It has four pages.
Glad that they gave not only four
pages?
See you next time!
I'm going to eat it.
How do you eat your favorite kinako?
Do you know how to eat it?
I think there are various ways, such as
eating it with a laughing face or eating
it with a kinako.
I eat it as it is.
I like to eat it with my mouth full of
it.
It's best.
It's really the first time I've eaten
it.
It's amazing, but I like yogurt.
It's a sweet.
It looks good.
It's like a cola in my mouth.
It's good.
It was good.
It's interesting.
It's difficult.
There are two questions left.
We all have a delicate taste.
The last question is 2 points.
I'll go to the next one.
I have a chance to win.
Please subscribe to this channel.
The last question.
The second question.
What is the most surprising vending
machine that you found recently?
Did you say that before?
No, I didn't.
Did you find it recently?
Very recently.
What is it?
It's not here.
This might be it.
This was difficult.
I don't want to answer.
There are two answers, so if you get
one of them, you can say OK.
Let's answer one by one.
Apple.
What?
1000 yen vending machine.
Crepe.
Soup stock.
Pancake.
There was soup stock.
But it's a roadside.
Oden.
Yes, it's a roadside.
It's difficult.
Please.
What is the most surprising vending
machine you have found recently?
What do you think it is?
Ramen vending machine.
Ramen vending machine and Monja vending
machine.
Do you know which one is which?
I'm Oharu who loves ramen.
I'm Akari.
Ramen?
No, ramen.
I found a picture of ramen.
It costs 1,000 yen.
I can't believe it.
Don't try to lie.
Do you put hot water in it?
No, I don't.
It's a bag.
It's like a frozen noodle.
I didn't know that.
The last one.
I'm scared.
It's a punishment game.
How many points do you want?
Do you prefer Oharu's point system or
Akari's?
3%.
What is 3%?
If you get it right, you'll get 3
points.
3 points?
2 points is fine.
I'm trying to be a queen.
2?
1 is fine.
I'm trying to be a queen.
Then, 2 points.
2 points.
If you get it right, you'll get 2
points.
Here is the question.
Q.Aki-chan's earphone started to break
more. How did it break this time?
The one with the wire?
Yes, the one with the wire.
I heard the sound of the wire.
I haven't changed it yet.
It's broken.
I don't know anymore.
What's the matter?
I'll write down what I've been through.
The hint is 50% of the time.
I see.
I'm smart.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Oh, no. I lost.
Are you OK?
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
OK, everyone.
This is the last question.
You have a chance to win back.
I don't know.
Please show us the answer.
Ear?
Which ear is broken?
I can't hear one of my ears.
I can't hear the right ear.
I lost.
You're right.
I can't hear one of my ears.
Please watch the video.
I'm scared.
Your earphone is broken.
How do you feel about that?
I said my earphone is broken
because I can hear the sound of the
earphone.
How do you think
my earphone is broken?
Let's think about it.
I don't know.
The answer is
I can't hear the right ear.
The sound is too small.
I'll raise the volume.
I can hear only my left ear.
I'm sorry.
Let's think about it.
How do you feel about that?
I can't hear the sound.
Did you use your earphone?
Yes.
I can hear the sound.
I'm scared.
It was a magic.
I was confused with my left ear.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I thought it was a secret.
The winner of this time is Hiori.
I did it.
I'm scared.
The winner of this time is Hiori.
Hiori got 4 points.
I think it would be good if she could
compete with me.
I'm happy.
It's a penalty game.
I'm so happy.
Please tell me your plans.
I'll make it myself.
Why did I say a lot of jokes?
I'll make everyone like Pokemon.
That's good.
I'll do my best.
I'm happy but I'm not sure if I'm
right.
I'm so happy but I'm not sure if I'm
I'm a Juriakio.
I haven't been the correct answer yet.
Me neither.
I was aiming for the first one.
I'm so happy.
But I think Juria is right.
I'm sure.
I was right at the end.
I'm done.
I'm going to do it.
My name is Pocchaman.
I'm a heart.
This part is a heart.
I drew three eyelashes.
Please show it to the camera.
I'm loved by you.
I'm Pocchaman.
I'm a heart.
Please use this part.
What kind of power does she have?
She makes everyone love her.
What does she make everyone love?
Her mouth.
Her nose.
She makes everyone love her.
Does she have a beam?
She has a beam.
She has three eyelashes.
She sticks them to everyone.
I see.
What kind of power does she have?
I'm lonely.
What level does she have?
She is...
She has three eyelashes.
She is cute.
That's all for today.
We got a lot of information from Aki-
chan.
I'm sure.
I'm surprised that so many of us got
the right answer.
I thought it was a small number.
It's not that difficult.
There were a lot of information that we
didn't know.
It was a great job.
Please subscribe to our channel.
We'll do it one more time.
We'll do it once.
I want to do it with a more difficult
problem.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you.
If you want to know more about Aki,
or if you want to go to a restaurant,
please subscribe to our channel.
What?
What are you writing?
I was writing something.
I was told the name of Pokemon,
but that's all I could think of.
And Tokiwaro has a new year special.
New year's day?
I don't know if there's a video of it,
but I think there is.
Maybe?
Maybe not?
Maybe there is.
Maybe it will be on the video.
Right?
Maybe we will be on the video.
Maybe there is something.
Maybe?
I don't know.
Please watch us a lot from the new
year.
Please.
Then,
lock on to your heart.
We are
Jyoutokimusi.
Bye-bye.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Last one.
Please.
Sorry.
We have a cool last one.
Good bye, goodbye, to me of yesterday.
The city lights are sparkling.
My heart is like a sunny day.
I make a sound in the puddle.
I'm a rainbow piano.
I wonder why, when I smile, the world
seems to shine
I can turn my umbrella and feel relaxed
If I don't, I can't walk
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I wonder if I'll get wet and cold again
somewhere
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I want to share my feelings with you
There's still a view I've never seen
before
Let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colorful
I draw a fragment of the future
on the canvas of my damaged heart
It will guide me
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Goodbye to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a flower
I cry and cry
I wear a rainbow dress